https://timg.co.nz/privacy-policy/

TransformOur Transform range of solutions allow your business information to be turned into knowledge. Securely convert your data and information into a valuable resource, leveraging it through efficiency, order and accessibility
Automated Accounts PayableStreamline your accounts payable processesCustomised Workflow SolutionsAutomate business processes and decision makingImaging and Document CaptureFile digitisation and data extractionLitigation Support and eDiscovery ServicesExtract metadata and electronic filesManageOur Manage range of solutions are designed to give you the visibility and control you need to manage your information, meet regulatory requirements and gain peace of mind that your information is securely protected
BackOnlineCloud storage and disaster recoveryFileSaverDigitise your file and prepay its lifetime costOffsite Backup Tape StorageVault based media storageRecords ManagementSecure document storage and archivingTIMG 3PLSecure warehousing and logisticsDestroyOur Destroy range of solutions ensure no security threats arise from discarded information. We offer a range of services to securely destroy sensitive business information to ensure it does not get into the wrong hands
Document DestructionSecure document destruction and paper recycling: in bins or in bulke-WasteSecure destruction of unwanted electronic equipmentOther Destruction ServicesSecurely destroy bulk paper, digital media and other non-hazardous materialAbout UsResourcesCase StudiesContactCOVID0800 SECURITYHelpSAFE LoginEnquiry
Solutions
By IndustryFind out how your industry benefits from our solutions
TIMG for FinanceTIMG for GovernmentTIMG for HealthcareTIMG for LegalTransformOur Transform range of solutions allow your business information to be turned into knowledge. Securely convert your data and information into a valuable resource, leveraging it through efficiency, order and accessibility
Automated Accounts PayableStreamline your accounts payable processesCustomised Workflow SolutionsAutomate business processes and decision makingImaging and Document CaptureFile digitisation and data extractionLitigation Support and eDiscovery ServicesExtract metadata and electronic filesManageOur Manage range of solutions are designed to give you the visibility and control you need to manage your information, meet regulatory requirements and gain peace of mind that your information is securely protected
BackOnlineCloud storage and disaster recoveryFileSaverDigitise your file and prepay its lifetime costOffsite Backup Tape StorageVault based media storageRecords ManagementSecure document storage and archivingTIMG 3PLSecure warehousing and logisticsDestroyOur Destroy range of solutions ensure no security threats arise from discarded information. We offer a range of services to securely destroy sensitive business information to ensure it does not get into the wrong hands
Document DestructionSecure document destruction and paper recycling: in bins or in bulke-WasteSecure destruction of unwanted electronic equipmentOther Destruction ServicesSecurely destroy bulk paper, digital media and other non-hazardous materialAbout UsResourcesCase StudiesContactCOVID0800 SECURITYHelpSAFE LoginEnquiry
icon-open
Created with Sketch.
menu-open
Created with Sketch.
Privacy Policy
Statement of intentThe Information Management Group (NZ) Limited recognises its responsibility, and is committed to, ensuring the privacy of your information.You may be asked to submit certain personal information in order to receive or use services from The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited. Such services include booking a courier and purchasing our products. We will treat any such personal information submitted by you and any information retrieved while using this website (Site”) in accordance with this Privacy Policy.The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited may, from time to time and in its sole discretion, modify, alter or otherwise change this Privacy Policy with or without notice to you. All such changes will be effective immediately upon the updating of the page on the Site at which the Privacy Policy is contained. You agree to check the Privacy Policy and be bound by the Privacy Policy that is in effect at the time at which you access the Site.If you have any further questions relating to this Privacy Policy, please email us at privacy@timg.co.nz
What this Privacy Policy coversCollection, use and storage of personal informationAccess to, editing and deleting personal informationInformation retrieved while using the SiteCookiesSecurityLinks to external website
Collection, use and storage of personal informationYou may browse and access information contained on the Site without providing personally identifiable information.Where you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information (e.g. if you apply for an account with us or email us), we will hold your personal information in accordance with the requirements set out in the Privacy Act 1993. In particular:Your personal information will be used only for the purposes for which it is collected and will be retained only for as long as is necessary to fulfil the purposes for which the information was collected (including any time that we are required by law to retain such information).We will not release your personal information to any third party except where required to, permitted to, by law, where you have authorised us to do so or where disclosure is connected to the purpose for which the information was collected.
Access to, editing and deleting personal informationYou can ask to see the personal information that we hold about you at any time by emailing us at privacy@timg.co.nz.You may also ask us to correct, alter or delete any personal information that we hold about you by emailing privacy@timg.co.nz. It is your responsibility to ensure that personal information provided to us is accurate.
Information retrieved while using the SiteSome information is automatically retrieved while you visit the Site. This information is outlined below. In the event that any personal information is collected, we will only use this information in aggregate form so that identify individual users cannot be identified.The Site automatically generates logs regarding your sessions on the Site such as the features you use, the actions that you take and the information that you access. The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited generally uses this information in statistical and aggregate formats to assess the effectiveness of the Site and to better understand your priorities and interests.We also log your IP address (the perceived location of your computer on the internet) whenever you use the Site. This is for system administration and troubleshooting purposes only.However, where you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g. through online forms), we will only use that information to undertake any transactions with you or communicate with you. We will keep any such information secure and will not disclose it to any third parties, except as authorised by statute or by you. To view any of your personal information held by us, or if you have any concerns about your personal information that we hold, please email privacy@timg.co.nz
CookiesThe Site uses cookies. If you elect to set or reset your phone number or PIN on the Site, a cookie will be placed on your computer. When you visit the Site again, the cookie will identify your computer to our web server and our web server will structure itself around the information provided. We do not use cookies to collect or store personal information about you but to improve the speed and reliability of our security system.
SecurityTo prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of any information supplied by you, The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited have put in place physical, electronic and managerial processes to protect your information.Additionally, all user information stored on the Site is protected from unauthorised access through the use of secure passwords, user PINs and other security procedures.For more information about our security procedures, please email privacy@timg.co.nz
Links to external websiteThe Site may contain information and links to external websites. The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited is not responsible for the privacy policies of any such external sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us.The information contained on this website is derived from many different sources. While The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited has taken all reasonable steps to ensure that all the information is from a reliable and reputable source and is accurate, it accepts no liability or responsibility for any acts or omissions, done or omitted in reliance, in whole or in part, on the information contained on this website. The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited takes no responsibility for the manner in which this information is subsequently used or the results of such use.To help users of this website to find related information, we provide links and references to third party websites. These links are provided for convenience and for information purposes only. Where we provide links on this website, we cannot guarantee that these links will work all of the time, have no control over the availability of linked pages, cannot accept responsibility for the content or reliability of the linked websites, do not necessarily endorse the views expressed within the linked pages or websites.The Information Management Group (NZ) Limited does not endorse or approve (expressly or implicitly) any website, organisation or people who have off-site links to this website.
Transform Solutions
Automated Accounts PayableCustomised Workflow SolutionsImaging and Document CaptureLitigation Support and eDiscovery ServicesManage Solutions
BackOnlineFileSaverOffsite Backup Tape StorageRecords ManagementTIMG 3PLDestroy Solutions
Document DestructionDestruction Bin Hire Informatione-WasteOther Destruction ServicesSolutions by Industry
TIMG for FinanceTIMG for GovernmentTIMG for HealthcareTIMG for LegalAbout Us
About UsBranch DetailsCertificationCorporate ResponsibilityPaper RecyclingOur Leadership TeamSecurityResources
ArticlesComplianceInnovateNewsYoutubeLinkedIn Back to Top© TIMG (NZ) LimitedPrivacy PolicyT’s & C’sFreightwaysTIMG Australia
